# Marcos Comelli

### Front End Software Engineer

e: marcoscomelli08@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcos-comelli/

## Summary

I've been interested in web development from a very young age. I remember myself experimenting with frontend technologies to build my first web page when I was just 14. I'm a Web Developer with a main focus on frontend but I also have considerable experience in backend. I am a very open person and always willing to try new experiences.

I finished my studies on computer engineering on 2018.

I always try to be up-to-date with the last trends and technologies to make the best apps.

# Work Experience

## Greencode Software (Full Stack Web Developer)

2015 - Present

### Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, Vue.js, React, JQuery, HTML, Css, Sass, Bootstrap
- Backend: Ruby on Rails, Node.js, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Mobile: Nativescript

#### Apps developed:

- + Medium like app for schools: App for sharing contents to school kids parents using Nativescript and Node.js with MongoDB on de backend
- + Bicycle races app: App for organizing bicycle races around the city made with Nativescript and Node.js with MongoDB on de backend.
- + Occupational medicine: 2 years on a project related to occupational medicine building the app with Ruby On Rails, .Net C#, PostgreSql and Testing with Rspec. Also used continuous integration and deployment. Team with 2 developers and one team leader.
- + Logistics App: 6 months building the front end of a big data app, using Vue.js with Redux and .Net on the backend. Basic usage of Docker. I was a developer in a team with 2 more developers, one team leader, a product owner and a scrum master.

### Kelawar (Co-Founder)

#### Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, Vue.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Leaflet
- Backend: ASP.NET Core, PostgreSQL, C#, LINQ, Entity Framework
- Raspberry Pi

Currently working with a team of 5 people to build a data collection app. It aims to collect data of customers visiting a shop, so that the owner can access multiple stats about who is visiting and therefore improve their

business. Get more info at  $\underline{\text{kelawar.com}}$ 

### Axum (Full Stack Web Developer)

2014 - 2015

#### Technologies:

- Frontend: Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.
- Backend: ASP.NET Framework, SQL Server, C#, NHibernate

My team was in charge of building and maintaining an order management app. I started doing multiple front end tasks using HTML, Javascript, CSS and Grunt. Then I did various tasks on the back end with .Net MVC, C# and Ms Sql Server, such as making improvements and implementing new features. There were 5 developers in the team. We handled the version management with GIT

## Personal Projects

## Web page for holiday chalet renting

I built a webpage from scratch for a holiday chalet renting business that previously had zero online presence. I integrated it with a gallery so that the hole place could be viewed, as well as creating a contact form so that the potential customers could ask the owners questions and make bookings.

# Key Skills

Javascript	HTML	MsSql Server	Scrum
Vue.js	Ruby On Rails	Git	Lean
CSS	Postgresql	Nativescript	

## Education

Universidad Nacional de La Matanza (UNLaM)

Computer engineering (2012 - 2018)

Instituto Madero (High School)

Electronic Technician Degree

## Languages

Spanish (Native)
English (Cambridge First Certificate)
Portuguese (Intermediate Level)